coolnameideas.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Cool Name Ideas

‘Cool Name Ideas’ is a trading name of Justin March

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.

By using our website and agreeing to this policy, you consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy.

### (1)      Credit

This document was created using an [SEQ Legal](http://www.seqlegal.com/free-legal-documents/privacy-policy) template.

### (2)      What information do we collect?

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal information:

(a) information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website (including your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views and website navigation paths);

(b) information that you provide to us when registering with our website including your email address;

(c) information that you provide when completing your profile on our website (including your name, profile pictures, gender, date of birth, relationship status, interests and hobbies, educational details and employment details);

(d) information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our email notifications and/or newsletters (including your name and email address);

(e) information that you provide to us when using the services on our website, or that is generated in the course of the use of those services (including the timing, frequency and pattern of service use);

(f) information that you post to our website for publication on the internet (including your user name, your profile pictures and the content of your posts);

(g) information contained in or relating to any communication that you send to us or send through our website (including the communication content and metadata associated with the communication); and

(h) any other personal information that you choose to send to us.

Before you disclose to us the personal information of another person, you must obtain that person’s consent to both the disclosure and the processing of that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy policy.

### (3)      About cookies

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server.

Cookies can be used by web servers to identity and track users as they navigate different pages on a website and identify users returning to a website.

Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies.

A persistent cookie consists of a text file sent by a web server to a web browser, which will be stored by the browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date (unless deleted by the user before the expiry date).

A session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.

Below is a list of the cookies our website places on your computer.

If you object to the use of the following types of cookie it is our opinion that the very best way to handle this is to put a stop to them across all of the sites that you browse. Below the list of cookies you will find instructions on removing or blocking cookies. If you are not happy about us dropping cookies on your computer and cannot or do not want to remove or block cookies at a browser level you must not use our website.

### (4)      Third party and analytics cookies

When you use our website, you may also be sent third party cookies.

Our advertisers / service providers may send you cookies. They may use the information they obtain from your use of their cookies:

(a)            to track your browser across multiple websites;

(b)            to build a profile of your web surfing; and

(c)            to distinguish you from other users of the website allowing us to provide you with a better user experience.

### WordPress

These cookies are only set if you visit our blog and leave a comment on one of our posts they are believed to be an integral part of our website’s functionality.  These cookies allow us to distinguish you from other users of the website which helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website.  For information about the data WordPress’s cookies contain, [click here](http://codex.wordpress.org/WordPress_Cookies).

### WordPress Cookie Names:

comment_author_  
comment_author_email_  
comment_author_url_

### Google Analytics

These cookies are used to collect information about how you use our site, but not to identify you as an individual. We use the information to help improve the site content and usability. The cookies collect information such as the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited.  For information about the data Google Analytics’ cookies contain, [click here](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html).

#### Google Analytics Cookie Names:

__utma  
__utmb  
__utmc  
__utmz  
_ga  
_gat

### Google DoubleClick

These cookies are associated with the DoubleClick for Publishers service from Google. Its purpose is to do with the showing of adverts on the site.

Google AdSense is an advertising service provided by Google. this site uses the “Doubleclick” Cookie, which tracks use of this site and user behavior concerning ads, products and the services we offer.

You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [Google Ad Preferences](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/) page, and if you want to you can [opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/) or [permanently using a browser plugin](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin).

To find out about DoubleClick cookies and how to control those cookies, go to <http://www.google.co.uk/policies/privacy/ads/>.

#### Google DoubleClick Cookie Names:

DSID  
IDE  
__gads  
_drt_  
test_cookie  
id

### Google Tracking and Safe Browsing

Google tracking and safe browsing cookies. Google’s NID and PREF cookies are set by browsers to protect users against known intrusive sites. If you arrive at one of these sites it allows your browser to take action or notify you. Users can stop these cookies being set by turning off their browser’s ‘safe browsing’ mode.  [More information about Google’s privacy policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/policies/privacy/).

#### Google Tracking and Safe Browsing Cookies Names:

NID  
PREF

### Embedded YouTube Videos

To track visitor views, and to remember user preferences when viewing YouTube videos embedded in our website web pages. [More information about YouTube cookies](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).

#### Embedded YouTube Videos Cookie Names:

PREF  
VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE  
YSC

### Commission Junction

We use Commission Junction to provide advertising on this website. You can find information on Commission Junction’s privacy policies and use of cookies at this url: <http://www.cj.com/legal/privacy_web_user.html>.

#### Commission Junction Cookie Names:

Unavailable.

### (5)      Cookies and personal information

Cookies do not contain any information that personally identifies you, but personal information that we store about you may be linked, by us, to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

### (6)      Blocking cookies

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies. For example:

(a)            in Internet Explorer (version 9) you can block cookies using the cookie handling override settings available by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy” and then “Advanced”;

(b)            in Firefox (version 16) you can block all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Options”, “Privacy”, selecting “Use custom settings for history” from the drop-down menu, and unticking “Accept cookies from sites”; and

(c)            in Chrome (version 23), you can block all cookies by accessing the “Customise and control” menu, and clicking “Settings”, “Show advanced settings” and “Content settings”, and then selecting “Block sites from setting any data” under the “Cookies” heading.

Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites.

If you block cookies, you will not be able to use all the features on this website.

### (7)      Deleting cookies

You can also delete cookies already stored on your computer. For example:

(a)            in Internet Explorer (version 9), you must manually delete cookie files (you can find instructions for doing so at http://support.microsoft.com/kb/278835);

(b)            in Firefox (version 16), you can delete cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Options”, “Privacy” and then “Show Cookies”, and then clicking “Remove All Cookies”; and

(c)            in Chrome (version 23), you can delete all cookies by accessing the “Customise and control” menu, and clicking “Settings”, “Show advanced settings” and “Clear browsing data”, and then selecting “Delete cookies and other site and plug-in data” before clicking “Clear browsing data”.

Again, doing this may have a negative impact on the usability of many websites.

### (8)      Using your personal information

Personal information submitted to us via this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

We may use your personal information to:

(a)      administer the website;

(b)      improve your browsing experience by personalising and improving the website content;

(c)      enable your use of the services available on the website;

(d)      send you goods purchased via the website, and supply to you services purchased via the website;

(e)      send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you;

(f)      send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;

(g)      send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;

(h)      send you our newsletter and other marketing communications relating to our business or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties which we think may be of interest to you, by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (and you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications);

(i)       provide third parties with statistical information about our users – but this information will not be used to identify any individual user;

(j)      deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website;

(k)      keep the website secure and prevent fraud; and

(l)       verify compliance with the terms and conditions governing the use of the website.

Where you submit personal information for publication on our website, we will publish and otherwise use that information in accordance with the licence you grant to us.

We will not, without your express consent, provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.

All our website financial transactions are handled through our payment services provider, PayPal. You can review the PayPal privacy policy at [www.paypal.com](https://www.paypal.com/). We will share information with PayPal only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make via our website, refunding such payments and dealing with complaints and queries relating to such payments and refunds.

### (9)    Disclosures

We may disclose your personal information to any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this privacy policy.

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group of companies (this means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and all its subsidiaries) insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this privacy policy.

In addition, we may disclose your personal information:

(a)      to the extent that we are required to do so by law;

(b)      in connection with any ongoing or prospective legal proceedings;

(c)      in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk);

(d)    to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset that we are (or are contemplating) selling; and

(e)    to any person who we reasonably believe may apply to a court or other competent authority for disclosure of that personal information where, in our reasonable opinion, such court or authority would be reasonably likely to order disclosure of that personal information.

Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.

### (10)    International data transfers

Information which you provide may be transferred to countries (including the United States, Japan or _other countries_ ) which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the European Economic Area.

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available, via the internet, around the world. We cannot prevent the use or misuse of such information by others.

You expressly agree to such transfers of personal information.

### (11)    Security of your personal information

We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password and firewall-protected) servers.

All electronic transactions entered into via the website will be protected by encryption technology.

You acknowledge that the transmission of information over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.

You are responsible for keeping your password and other login details confidential. We will not ask you for your password (except when you log in to the website).

### (12)    Policy amendments

We may update this privacy policy from time to time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.

We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by email.

### (13)    Your rights

You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. Provision of such information will be subject to:

(a)      the payment of a fee (currently fixed at GBP 10); and

(b)      the supply of appropriate evidence of your identity (for this purpose, we will usually accept a photocopy of your passport certified by a solicitor or bank plus an original copy of a utility bill showing your current address).

We may withhold such personal information to the extent permitted by law.

You may instruct us not to process your personal information for marketing purposes, by sending an email to us. In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal information for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt out of the use of your personal information for marketing purposes.

### (14)    Third party websites

The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.

### (15)    Updating information

Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.

### (16)    Contact

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal information, please write to us by email using our contact form or by post to 1 Bathleaze, Kings Stanley, Stonehouse, Gloucestershire, GL10 3JN, UK.

### (17)    Data controller

The data controller responsible in respect of the information collected on this website is Justin March.
